Lewis W. Douglas papers, 1859-1974 (bulk 1880-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Lewis W. Douglas Papers, 1906-1974
  - Subseries I: Personal Material, 1923-1974
    - Personal Correspondence
      - Benedict, P.C. and family. 1965-1973 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Benson, Rex. 1956-1970 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Bing, Rudolph. 1966-1972 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Bingham, Sally and Anthony. 1961-1966 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Braga, Mrs. George. 1972-1973 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Brunie, Harry C. and Anna. 1968-1972 (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - Call, Asa V. 1961-1971 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Carter, Marshall S. 1950-1967 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Casey, Richard. 1970-1973 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Clemenceau, Pierre B. 1952-1973 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Colquhoun, James and son. 1927-1970 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Cosulich, Bernice. 1952-1954 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Cousins, Norman. 1964-1972 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Cowdray, John and Elizabeth. 1954-1974 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Cuthbert, H.T. 1930-1956 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Dahlberg, Henry and Family. 1960-1972 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Davies, Daniel. 1965-1966 (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Davison, Daniel P. 1957-1973 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Davison, Endicott Peabody. 1951-1971 (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - Davison, F. Trubee. 1930-1974 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Davison, Gates. 1965-1971 (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - Davison, Harry P. 1933-1960 (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - DeGolyer, Everett. 1950-1973 (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - Douglas, James H. Jr. 1936-1973 (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - Ellinwood family. 1930-1973 (Box 80, Folder 19-20)
      - Fairbanks, Douglas Jr. 1956-1968 (Box 80, Folder 21)
      - Hanes, John W. and "Hopie." 1960-1973 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Hayward, Leland and Pamela. 1965-1971 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Hendel, Charles W. 1941-1943 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Hepburn, Katharine and Tracy, Spencer. 1955-1971 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Hull, Roger and Rosalie. 1965-1974 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Kaye, Danny. 1958-1972 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Kidder, Alfred V. 1926-1956 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Kinsolving, Rev. Arthur B. and family. 1961-1969 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Lamont, Thomas. 1952-1971 (Box 81, Folder 9-10)
      - Lewis, Wilmarth Sheldon. 1969-1973 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Lowery, Fred W. 1927-1950 (Box 81, Folder 12-13)
      - McCafferey, Robert L. 1958-1973 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - McCarthy, Frank. 1958-1973 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - MacLeish, Archibald. 1965-1970 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - MacNider, Hanford. 1928-1968 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Massigli, Rene and Odette. 1960-1973 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - Minotto, James. 1929-1971 (Box 81, Folder 19-20)
      - Mitchell, Rev. Walter. 1963-1968 (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Moore, Robert L. 1939-1942 (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - O'Neill, Robert K. 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Overfield, P.D. and Virginia. 1933-1936 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Pagliai, Bruno and Oberon, Merle. 1961-1971 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Parsons, Geoffrey and family. 1963-1968 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Pol Roger, Odette. 1956-1973 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Purvis, Arthur B. 1938-1941 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Robertson, Alan. 1969-1970 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - roderick, Thomas E. 1956-1959 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Rowan, Leslie and Judy. 1967-1973 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Sanger, Drs. Stuart and Grant. 1956-1970 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Shepherd, Donald C. 1926-1939 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Silvercrys, Robert and Family. 1961-1972 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - Simpson, Harry. 1929-1956 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Sinclair, Robert. 1952-1973 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Holbrook. 1971-1973 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - Sutcliffe, Hiram and Thomas. 1926-1929 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - Swanton, Hobart P. 1932-1955 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - Warburg, Edward M.M. 1970-1973 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - Welby, Jane. 1965-1973 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Wheeler-Bennett, John. 1963-1974 (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence. no date (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous clippings about Arizona Friends. no date (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence. 1926-1954 (Box 83, Folder 1-10)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence. 1955-1959 (Box 84, Folder 1-5)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence. 1960-1974 (Box 85, Folder 1-12)
    - Hunting, fishing, cattle
      - Hunting. 1940-1973 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Fishing, general correspondence. 1927-1973 (Box 86, Folder 2-3)
      - Fishing, correspondence, LaMonte Belnap. 1957-1965 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Fishing, correspondence, Dwight Webster. 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Fishing, trips. no date (Box 86, Folder 6-7)
      - Fishing, trips by others. no date (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Fishing, LWD's review of fishing book, An Angler's Entonology, by J.R. Harris. 1952 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Cattle. 1957-1972 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Horses
      - Correspondence. 1947-1975 (Box 87, Folder 1-4)
      - Photographs, Forward Runner. no date (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, various. no date (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Tabulated Racing Records, notebook. no date (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Horse book. no date (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Automobiles
      - General correspondence. 1927-1974 (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
      - Insurance Correspondence. 1927-1933, 1942-1970 (Box 89, Folder 5-6)
      - Accident. 1931 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Accident. 1959 (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - Traffic problems. 1932-1973 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Books
      - Books, etc. (received as gifts). 1960-1973 (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
      - Books, etc. (requested and/or purchased by LWD). 1945-1973 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Books, etc. (distribution of Douglas Family books: Lands Forlorn, New England and New France, Old France in the New World). 1965-1973 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - LWD's books (lists, repair of). no date (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence regarding books by others, Connell, Brian. 1960 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence regarding books by others, Young, Herbert V. 1962-1974 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence regarding books by others, Myrick, David F. 1964-1974 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence regarding books by others, Smith, Thomas G. 1972-1974 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Magazine subscriptions. no date (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Personal Miscellany
      - Addresses. no date (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Art. 1927-1973 (Box 91, Folder 2-3)
      - Baseball tickets. 1957-1970 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Clothing, jewelry, cane, etc. 1926-1973 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Dogs. 1921-1972 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Entertainment. 1953-1959 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - 2 notebooks containing addresses and telephone numbers. no date (Box 91)
    - Christmas Greetings
      - Christmas greetings. 1927-1932 (Box 92)
      - Christmas greetings. 1933-1959 (Box 93)
      - Christmas greetings. 1960-1973 (Box 94)
    - Trips & Vacations
      - Trips and vacations. 1927-1940 (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
      - Italian travel brochures. 1930s (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Trip to England. June-August 1951 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Trip to South Africa. January-February 1952 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Trip to England and Finland. June-August 1952 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Trip to England. September-October 1953 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Trip to England. May 1954 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Trip to England. June-July 1955 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Trip to Europe, South Africa, returning via Greece. May-June 1956 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Trip to England, Spain, etc. May-August 1957 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Trips (various). 1958-1959 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Trip to Europe and South Africa. May-July 1961 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Trip to Europe and South Africa. May-August 1962 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Trip to Europe and South Africa. May-July 1963 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Trip to Europe and South Africa. May-July 1964 (Box 96, Folder 4-5)
      - Trip to London and South Africa. September 1965 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Trip to Europe and South Africa. May-June 1966 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Trip to Hawaii. August 1966 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Trip to London and South Africa. June-July 1967 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Trip to Montreal, Canada. August-September 1967 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Trip to London and South Africa (cancelled). June-July 1968 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Trip to London. January 1969 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Trip to London and South Africa. May-July 1969 (Box 97, Folder 2-3)
      - Trip to Europe and South Africa. June-July 1970 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Trip to London. June 1971 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Proposed Alaskan-Canadian cruise (not taken). August 1971 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Trip to London and Paris. June-July 1972 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Trip to South Africa with Mrs. Ralph Ellinwood. December 1972-January 1973 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Trip to Europe. June-July 1973 (Box 97, Folder 9-10)
    - Passports and Travel Correspondence
      - Passports. no date (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Travel correspondence, miscellaneous and various. 1960-1973 (Box 98, Folder 2-4)
      - Travel correspondence, American Airline Personnel. 1960-1973 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Travel correspondence, Charles C. Tillinghast, Trans World Airlines. 1966-1974 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Philanthropy, 1920-1974
      - Contributions to Charities and Organizations. 1920-1974 (Box 99, Folder 1-13)
      - Pantano Foundation, correspondence and transactions. 1955-1959 (Box 99, Folder 14)
      - Trubee Davison, Jr. Memorial Library, Groton School, Groton, MA. 1938 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Memorial window in St. John's Church, Bisbee, AZ. 1941 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Gift of Copper Minerals from James Douglas Collection to Smithsonian Institution. 1944 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Peace Corps School-to School program. 1966 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - New Organ for the Globe, AZ Presbyterian Church. 1966-1967 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Gift of LWD's Papers to the Universit of Arizona. 1968 (Box 100, Folder 6-7)
      - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum. 1969-1970 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Bisbee Council o the Arts and Humanities. 1970-1974 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation. 1971-1973 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Grenville Clark Fund at Dartmouth College. 1972-1974 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Loans. 1926-1954 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Personal gifts, Mikhail Sheyne. 1941-1942, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Personal gifts, Mary Kurmeier. 1941-1945 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Personal gifts, Margaret Miner. 1945-1973 (Box 101, Folder 3-4)
      - Personal gifts, William Morton Fullerton. 1952 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Personal gifts, Dorothy Partridge. 1952-1956 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Personal gifts, Katherine Peterson. 1955-1956 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Personal gifts, various. 1930-1957, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Taxes
      - Income Taxes. 1923-1946 (Box 102, Folder 1-10)
      - Income Taxes. 1947-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1-6)
      - Miscellaneous Taxes. no date (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Honorary Degrees & Awards
      - Harvard University, honorary degree. June 22, 1933 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Harvard University, consultant for Graduate School of Public Administration. 1937-1938 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - New York University, honorary degree. June 8, 1938 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Wesleyan University, honorary degree. June 19, 1938 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Brown University, honorary degree. June 20, 1938 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Princeton University, honorary degree. June 21, 1938 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Queen's College, Kingston, Canada, honorary degree. May 13, 1938 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Universit of Arizona, honorary degree. May 29, 1940 (Box 104, Folder 8-9)
      - University of California, honorary degree. March 19, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 10-12)
      - French Legion of Honor, Grand Croix. 1951 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Order of the Crown of Belgium, Grand Cross. June 5, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Columbia University, honorary degree. June 7, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Theodore Roosevelt Memorial Association, medal of honor. October 28, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - National Institute of Social Sciences, gold medal. November 8, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Dalhousie University, Halifax, Nova Scotia, honorary degree. December 1, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Order of the British Empire, honorary Knight Grand Cross. October 19, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 4-6)
      - University of Arizona, medallion of merit. December 15, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Newcomen Society in America, dinner honoring Douglas Family. October 19, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews, banquet honoring Mr. and Mrs. Lewis W. Douglas. April 9, 1964 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous honors and awards. no date (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Proposed honorary degrees: Bates College, Yale University, St.Lawrence University, Jamestown College, and Dartmouth College. 1938-1959 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Houses & Property
      - Houses and Property, Washington, D.C. 1928-1932 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Houses and Property, Little Moose Lake, NY. 1927-1949 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Houses and Property, Zinsser property, Hastings, NY. 1960-1962 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Houses and Property, Stone Cottage, Hastings, NY. 1952 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Houses and Property, London, 29 Charles St. 1955-1957 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Houses and Property, London, 45 Chester Square. 1957 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Houses and Property, Tucson rental. 1953 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Houses and Property, Oregon. 1941-1946 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Houses and Property, Lowery property, Maricopa County, AZ. 1945-1950 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Houses and Property, Power of Attorney. 1942 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Legal Residence, voting registration. 1926-1973 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Household furnishings. 1926-1972 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Jury duty. 1940-1973 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Rental of films for Christmas Eve at Hastings-on-Hudson, NY. December 24, 1927 (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - House and Property, 1 East End, NY. 1939 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - House and Property, 784 Park Ave, NY. 1947-1971 (Box 107, Folder 2-4)
      - House and Property, 784 Park Ave, NY, correspondence with tenants. 1965-1970 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - House and Property, 784 Park Ave, NY, leases. 1946-1951 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - House and Property, 834 Fifth Ave, NY. 1953-1968 (Box 107, Folder 7-8)
      - House and Property, 834 Fifth Ave, NY, correspondence with tenants. 1959-1964 (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Brophy-Douglas Ranch, correspondence. 1929-1956 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Brophy-Douglas Ranch, balance sheets. 1924-1953 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Phoenix house, correspondence. 1925-1938 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Phoenix house, blueprints for remodeling. 1924 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Phoenix house, legal papers, inventories, insurance. no date (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Phoenix house, sale correspondence. September 1946-July 1948 (Box 108, Folder 6-7)
      - Heard Building, Phoenix. 1926-1933 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Flagstaff Ranch (Dickey and White). 1930-1932 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Douglas, AZ property. 1941-1943 (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Pantano Farm (Hodges property). 1949-1961 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Jerome Property ("Small House"). 1938-1946 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Jerome Property ("Big House"). 1921-1958 (Box 109, Folder 3-8)
      - Jerome Property ("Big House"). 1959-1972 (Box 110, Folder 1-4)
      - Jereome Property ("Big House"), Dedication Ceremonies. October 7, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Douglas Livestock Company
      - Arizona Ranch, Sonoita. 1940-1944 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Souglas Livestock Company. 1945-1959 (Box 111, Folder 2-5)
      - Thurber Correspondence. December 1944-September 1949 (Box 111, Folder 6-7)
      - Ranch House Plans and Construction. 1945-1950 (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - Well-drilling and Peerless Pump Correspondence. 1945-1949 (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Material. no date (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Household Employees
      - Social Security Records. 1936-1958 (Box 112, Folder 1-5)
      - Correspondence regarding: Cora Babcock, Mary Sullivan, Emily Thresher, and others. 1927-1970 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Payroll Records (5 books). March 1952-November 1957 (Box 112)
    - Appointment Diaries
      - Appointment Diaries. 1940-1946, 1951-1953 (Box 113)
      - Appointment Diaries. 1954-1958 (Box 114)
      - Appointment Diaries. 1964-1968 (Box 115)
      - Appointment Diaries. 1964-1968 (Box 116)
      - Appointment Diaries. 1969-1974 (Box 117)
    - Reminiscences
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, Foreward. no date (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, Chapter I, Germany. no date (Box 118, Folder 2-3)
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, Chapter II, London and the Ambassador Years. no date (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, Chapter on the budget years. no date (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, last typing. September 1973 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1972-1973 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, Miscellaneous background material, notes, etc. no date (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - "Random Reminiscences" by LWD, Miscellaneous background material, notes, etc. no date (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Congressional and Budget years, Ambassadorship, correspondence. 1964-1973 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - U.S. Control Council and Germany, correspondence. 1960-1972 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - Marshall Plan and Berlin Blockade, correspondence. 1971-1972 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - Marshall Plan and Berlin Blockade, correspondence. 1962-1970 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - Council of Foreign Ministers, Germany, Marshall Plan, correspondence. 1947, 1971-1973 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - Sargent, James E., correspondence. August 1969-June 1974 (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
      - Sargent, James E., Interviews with LWD (tapes). 1972 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - Sargent, James E., Interviews with LWD (transcripts). 1972 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - Sargent, James E., Interviews with LWD (transcript, Budget Years). 1972 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - Sargent, James E., Interviews with LWD (transcript, miscellaneous questions). 1972 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - Sargent, James E., fragment of manuscript. no date (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - Columbia University Oral History Interview with LWD. 1972 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      - Arizona State University, Carl Hayden Project, Interview with LWD. 1973 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Death of Lewis W. Douglas
      - Correspondence. January-April 1974 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Clippings. no date (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Letters of condolence to Mrs. Douglas, A-M. no date (Box 120, Folder 3-13)
      - Letters of condolence to Mrs. Douglas, N-Z. no date (Box 121, Folder 1-7)
      - Contributions in memory of LWD. no date (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Letters of condolence to son James S. Douglas. no date (Box 121, Folder 9-11)
  - Subseries II: State Legislature and Congress, 1923-1933
    - 6th Arizona State Legislature, 1923-1925
      - Colorado River Compact, correspondence. January 1923-March 1924 (Box 122, Folder 1-2)
      - Colorado River Compact, speeches, reports, and article. no date (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Colorado River Compact, miscellaneous material. no date (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Joint Committee on Irrigation and Agriculture. no date (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Highway Investigating Committee. no date (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Propose Legislation, miscellaneous. no date (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - 6th Legislature, session laws. no date (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous material. no date (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Speech to the Sons and Daughters of the American Revolution. February 22, 1924 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Political Campaign, 1926
      - Correspondence, general. 1926 (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
      - Correspondence. no date (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - Campaign expenses. no date (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - Nomination papers, speeches, campaign advertising. no date (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - Election returns. no date (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous material. no date (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - Democratic National Committee, press releases. 1926-1927 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - Clippings. 1926-1927 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - 70th Congress, Administration, 1927-1929
      - Correspondence, general. 1927-1929 (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, House of Representatives, miscellaneous, (includes diary for December 5-16, 1927). 1927 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, office. no date (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Arizona Legislature and other state officials. no date (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Salt River Valley Project and Verde River Irrigation Project. no date (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Applications for secretarial position. no date (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, regarding legislation. no date (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - Congressional committees. no date (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - Resolutions regarding legislation. no date (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - Letters of Introduction & Recommendation, subscriptions and newspapers. no date (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - Football games. no date (Box 124, Folder 12)
      - Requests, for various government publications. no date (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Requests, for U.S.D.A. publications. no date (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Requests, for Agricultural Yearbook. no date (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Requests, for information. no date (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Requests, miscellaneous. no date (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Congressional Record mailing list. no date (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - Various publications received and sent. no date (Box 125, Folder 7-10)
      - Job requests. no date (Box 125, Folder 11)
      - Speech, American Mining Congress. December 2, 1927 (Box 125, Folder 12)
      - Department of Agriculture. no date (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - Department of Agriculture (forest service). no date (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - Department of Commerce. no date (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Department of Justice. no date (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Department of Labor (bureau of immigration). no date (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Department of State, correspondence. no date (Box 126, Folder 6)
      - Department of State, publications and miscellaneous material. no date (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - Department of the Treasury. no date (Box 126, Folder 8)
      - Department of the Navy. no date (Box 126, Folder 9)
      - Post Office, general. no date (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - Post Office, air mail route. no date (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Post office, Arizona. no date (Box 127, Folder 3-4)
      - War Department, general. no date (Box 127, Folder 5-6)
      - War Department, Army post at Nogales, AZ. no date (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - War Department, Buckeye target range. no date (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - War Department, Citizens Military Training Camps. no date (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - Veterans Bureau, general. no date (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Veterans Bureau, Veterans Hospital, Tucson, AZ. no date (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - Veterans Bureau, Whipple Hospital, Prescott, AZ. no date (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - Department of the Interior, general correspondence. no date (Box 128, Folder 1)